<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cara Rust</title>
    <link>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cara Rust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dev.cararust.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Date</title>
      <link>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/the-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/the-date/</guid>
      <description>Swipe right, swipe left, swipe right … The only thing Lucas goes through faster than beer is the dates he goes on. Until he meets Maya, a down-to-earth mature girl who isn’t afraid of being herself. Lucas struggles to deepen the connection and realises he has not dealt with a previous loss in his life. Produced by Cara Rust Esperance Potgieter
Directed &amp;amp; Edited by Cara Rust
Director of Photography David Radosz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Made Simple</title>
      <link>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/english-made-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/english-made-simple/</guid>
      <description>In this absurd comedy, misfits Jake and James, entertain themselves at a pretentious party. &amp;lsquo;English Made Simple&amp;rsquo; explores the complexities of defining yourself as an outcast. Directed &amp;amp; Edited by Cara Rust Screenplay by Cara Rust based on the play by David Ives Production Sound Mix by Jannik Richter With Milan Struwig - Jack Natasha Govender - Jill Jaco van Niekerk - Jake Willem van Wyk - James
Camera - Shot entirely on a Samsung Galaxy S9 Gimbal - Osmo Mobile 2 App - Filmic Pro</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upper Mill - Slowly (Official Music Video)</title>
      <link>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/uppermill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/uppermill/</guid>
      <description>Slowly is a song about time and how routine can be mundane, yet, small moments of euphoria makes it all worth it. A banging drum verse turns into an explosive chorus with melodic vocals and harmonies. Directed &amp;amp; Edited by Cara Rust Upper Mill Band Website Camera - Shot entirely on a Samsung Galaxy S9 Gimbal - Osmo Mobile 2 App - Filmic Pro</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulb Flowers</title>
      <link>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/bulb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/bulb/</guid>
      <description>Zahn Rust, founder &amp;amp; owner of Bulb Flowers, shares her passion for blooms and why BULB is so superbly unique. Directed &amp;amp; Edited by Cara Rust Bulb Flowers Website Camera - Shot entirely on a Samsung Galaxy S9 Gimbal - Osmo Mobile 2 App - Filmic Pro</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Trendy Plant Stand</title>
      <link>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/diy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/diy/</guid>
      <description>Make a trendy plant stand with this easy tutorial. It&amp;rsquo;s a minor update that can transform any space in your home 🏠🔵 Takealot &amp;amp; Ryobi South Africa Edited by Cara Rust</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flat Fee Homes</title>
      <link>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/flat-fee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/flat-fee/</guid>
      <description>We ask our &amp;ldquo;expert&amp;rdquo; panel some seemingly simple real estate questions, See how they answered the first one&amp;hellip; Flat Fee Homes South Africa Edited by Cara Rust</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No-Churn Blueberry Ice Cream</title>
      <link>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/foodies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/foodies/</guid>
      <description>This EASY Blueberry Ice Cream is made with a secret ingredient that&amp;rsquo;ll blue your mind 💙⁣ Rose&amp;rsquo;s Cordial South Africa Edited by Cara Rust</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Zoo Story</title>
      <link>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/zoo-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev.cararust.com/posts/zoo-story/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Zoo Story&amp;rdquo; is a one-act play by Edward Albee that explores the themes of isolation, communication, and class conflict in modern society. The play takes place on a bench in New York City&amp;rsquo;s Central Park, where Peter, a middle-class executive, is approached by Jerry, a lonely and unpredictable stranger. As their conversation unfolds, Jerry&amp;rsquo;s sinister intentions become clear, leading to a violent and shocking conclusion that forces Peter to confront his own sense of identity and purpose in life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
